export const quizData = [
  {
    score: 0,
    id: 1,
    name: 'History of Madrid',
    isActive: true,
    coordinates: { latitude: 40.4168, longitude: -3.7038 }, // General coordinates for Madrid
    questions: [
      {
        question: 'In which year was Madrid declared the capital of Spain?',
        options: ['1500', '1561', '1605'],
        answer: '1561',
      },
      {
        question: 'Who was the king of Spain when Madrid became the capital?',
        options: ['Philip II', 'Charles I', 'Ferdinand VI'],
        answer: 'Philip II',
      },
      {
        question: 'What significant event took place in Madrid in 1808?',
        options: [
          'The Spanish Civil War',
          'The Peninsular War',
          'The Reconquista',
        ],
        answer: 'The Peninsular War',
      },
      {
        question:
          'Which famous painter depicted the "Third of May 1808" in Madrid?',
        options: ['Pablo Picasso', 'Francisco Goya', 'Salvador Dalí'],
        answer: 'Francisco Goya',
      },
      {
        question: 'What major structure was completed in Madrid in 1755?',
        options: [
          'The Royal Palace',
          'The Almudena Cathedral',
          'The Prado Museum',
        ],
        answer: 'The Royal Palace',
      },
      {
        question:
          'Which Spanish Civil War battle took place in Madrid in 1936?',
        options: [
          'Battle of the Ebro',
          'Siege of Madrid',
          'Battle of Guadalajara',
        ],
        answer: 'Siege of Madrid',
      },
      {
        question: 'What year did Madrid host the Olympic Games?',
        options: ['1984', '1992', '2020'],
        answer: '2020',
      },
      {
        question: 'Who was the architect of the Palacio de Cibeles?',
        options: [
          'Francisco Javier González',
          'Santiago Calatrava',
          'Antonio Gaudí',
        ],
        answer: 'Francisco Javier González',
      },
      {
        question:
          "What historic area is known as Madrid's oldest neighborhood?",
        options: ['Malasaña', 'La Latina', 'Chueca'],
        answer: 'La Latina',
      },
      {
        question: 'Which important treaty was signed in Madrid in 1492?',
        options: [
          'Treaty of Tordesillas',
          'Treaty of Alcáçovas',
          'Treaty of Utrecht',
        ],
        answer: 'Treaty of Alcáçovas',
      },
    ],
    success:
      'Moorish Roots of Madrid: The Foundation and Early Development\n\nMadrid, today one of the largest cities in Europe, has an unexpected origin—its roots trace back to the Moorish period when much of the Iberian Peninsula was under Muslim rule. The city was founded in the 9th century by Muhammad I, the Caliph of Cordoba, who built a fortress called *Al-Majrit* (from the Arabic "source of water") on the banks of the Manzanares River. This was not just a defensive structure but also a symbol of Moorish influence in the region.\n\nThe Moors developed an advanced irrigation and water supply system—known as *qanats*—that provided water to the fortress and surrounding settlements. This technical achievement allowed the city to thrive even in the hot and arid climate. The architecture of Madrid at that time was typically Islamic: narrow streets, mosques, and inner courtyards.\n\nAlthough Christian kingdoms captured Madrid in 1083, the Moorish legacy continued to influence the city\'s life. Street names, remnants of fortress walls, and hydraulic structures still remind us of the time when the small Al-Majrit was part of the vast Muslim world.',
  },
  {
    score: 0,
    id: 2,
    name: 'Culture of Madrid',
    isActive: false,
    coordinates: { latitude: 40.4146, longitude: -3.7004 }, // Coordinates for Plaza Mayor, a cultural landmark
    questions: [
      {
        question:
          'What is the traditional Spanish dish originating from Madrid called?',
        options: ['Paella', 'Cocido Madrileño', 'Gazpacho'],
        answer: 'Cocido Madrileño',
      },
      {
        question: 'Which famous festival takes place in Madrid in May?',
        options: ['San Isidro', 'La Tomatina', 'Running of the Bulls'],
        answer: 'San Isidro',
      },
      {
        question: "What is the name of Madrid's main opera house?",
        options: ['Teatro Español', 'Teatro Real', 'Teatro de la Abadía'],
        answer: 'Teatro Real',
      },
      {
        question:
          'Which museum in Madrid is famous for its collection of European art?',
        options: [
          'Museo del Prado',
          'Museo Thyssen-Bornemisza',
          'Museo Reina Sofía',
        ],
        answer: 'Museo del Prado',
      },
      {
        question:
          'What is the name of the famous market in Madrid known for its tapas?',
        options: [
          'Mercado de San Miguel',
          'Mercado de Antón Martín',
          'Mercado de Vallehermoso',
        ],
        answer: 'Mercado de San Miguel',
      },
      {
        question: 'Which popular dance is associated with Spanish culture?',
        options: ['Flamenco', 'Salsa', 'Tango'],
        answer: 'Flamenco',
      },
      {
        question:
          'What is the name of the annual film festival held in Madrid?',
        options: [
          'Festival de Cannes',
          'Festival de San Sebastián',
          'Festival de Cine de Madrid',
        ],
        answer: 'Festival de Cine de Madrid',
      },
      {
        question: 'Which historic square is the heart of Madrid?',
        options: ['Plaza de España', 'Puerta del Sol', 'Plaza Mayor'],
        answer: 'Puerta del Sol',
      },
      {
        question:
          'What type of traditional Spanish music is often performed in Madrid?',
        options: ['Bossa Nova', 'Flamenco', 'Jazz'],
        answer: 'Flamenco',
      },
      {
        question:
          'What is the name of the famous street known for shopping in Madrid?',
        options: ['Gran Vía', 'Paseo del Prado', 'Calle Serrano'],
        answer: 'Gran Vía',
      },
    ],
    success:
      'The Reconquista and Christianization of Madrid\n\nMadrid, which had been under Muslim rule since the 9th century, became part of the Christian world after its capture by King Alfonso VI of Castile in 1083. This event marked an important stage in the Reconquista, the gradual reclaiming of the Iberian Peninsula by Christian kingdoms.\n\nAfter the city was conquered, Christian forces began the active Christianization of Madrid. Mosques were converted into churches, including the famous Al-Mudena mosque, which was transformed into the first Christian church. Later, the Almudena Cathedral was built here, dedicated to the Virgin Mary of Almudena, who became the patron saint of Madrid.\n\nThe conquest also encouraged the resettlement of Christian populations in the city. New monasteries and defensive fortifications were constructed, symbolizing the power of the Christian kings. Madrid gradually evolved from a Moorish fortress into an important center of Christian influence, laying the foundation for its future role as the capital of Spain.',
  },
  {
    score: 0,
    id: 3,
    name: 'Landmarks of Madrid',
    isActive: false,
    coordinates: { latitude: 40.4180, longitude: -3.7144 }, // Coordinates for Royal Palace of Madrid
    questions: [
      {
        question: 'What is the most famous royal palace in Madrid?',
        options: [
          'Palacio de Cibeles',
          'Palacio Real',
          'Palacio de los Duques de Osuna',
        ],
        answer: 'Palacio Real',
      },
      {
        question: 'Which iconic statue can be found at the Puerta del Sol?',
        options: [
          'El Oso y el Madroño',
          'La Dama de Elche',
          'El Caballero de Gracia',
        ],
        answer: 'El Oso y el Madroño',
      },
      {
        question:
          'What is the name of the park that is the largest green space in Madrid?',
        options: ['Retiro Park', 'Parque del Oeste', 'Casa de Campo'],
        answer: 'Retiro Park',
      },
      {
        question:
          'Which famous art museum features works by Velázquez and Goya?',
        options: [
          'Museo del Prado',
          'Museo Reina Sofía',
          'Museo Thyssen-Bornemisza',
        ],
        answer: 'Museo del Prado',
      },
      {
        question: 'What is the name of the famous clock tower in Madrid?',
        options: [
          'Torre de Madrid',
          'Torre de Cibeles',
          'Puerta del Sol Clock',
        ],
        answer: 'Puerta del Sol Clock',
      },
      {
        question: "Which structure is a symbol of Madrid's skyline?",
        options: ['Torres KIO', 'Torre Picasso', 'Edificio España'],
        answer: 'Torres KIO',
      },
      {
        question:
          'What is the name of the ancient Egyptian temple located in Madrid?',
        options: ['Temple of Debod', 'Temple of Karnak', 'Temple of Luxor'],
        answer: 'Temple of Debod',
      },
      {
        question:
          'Which square is known for its beautiful architecture and historical significance?',
        options: ['Plaza Mayor', 'Plaza de Cibeles', 'Plaza de la Villa'],
        answer: 'Plaza Mayor',
      },
      {
        question:
          'What is the name of the bridge that connects Madrid to the other side of the river?',
        options: [
          'Puente de Toledo',
          'Puente de Segovia',
          'Puente de la Reina',
        ],
        answer: 'Puente de la Reina',
      },
      {
        question: 'Which historic building houses the Spanish Parliament?',
        options: [
          'Palacio de las Cortes',
          'Palacio de la Moncloa',
          'Palacio Real',
        ],
        answer: 'Palacio de las Cortes',
      },
    ],
    success:
      "Medieval Madrid: Expansion and Fortification\n\nDuring the Middle Ages, Madrid evolved from a small frontier town into a significant stronghold under Christian rule. After its capture by Alfonso VI in the late 11th century, the city's strategic position on the frontier between Christian and Muslim territories spurred its growth and development.\n\nIn the 12th and 13th centuries, Madrid's population began to increase, and the town expanded beyond its original walls. New fortifications were built to protect the growing city, including a larger defensive wall and several watchtowers. These fortifications helped defend Madrid during turbulent periods, particularly from Moorish counterattacks.\n\nThe city's economy also began to develop, driven by agriculture, trade, and its role as a regional administrative center. Several churches and monasteries were established, reinforcing its Christian identity. By the 15th century, Madrid was a well-fortified and prosperous medieval town, setting the stage for its eventual rise to prominence as the capital of Spain.",
  },
  {
    score: 0,
    id: 4,
    name: 'Sports in Madrid',
    isActive: false,
    coordinates: { latitude: 40.4110, longitude: -3.6883 }, // Coordinates for Santiago Bernabéu Stadium
    questions: [
      {
        question: 'Which football club is based in Madrid?',
        options: ['FC Barcelona', 'Atlético Madrid', 'Sevilla FC'],
        answer: 'Atlético Madrid',
      },
      {
        question: "What is the name of Madrid's main stadium?",
        options: ['Camp Nou', 'Santiago Bernabéu', 'Metropolitano'],
        answer: 'Santiago Bernabéu',
      },
      {
        question: 'In which year did Spain host the FIFA World Cup?',
        options: ['1982', '1990', '1998'],
        answer: '1982',
      },
      {
        question: 'Which famous tennis tournament is held annually in Madrid?',
        options: ['Australian Open', 'Madrid Open', 'French Open'],
        answer: 'Madrid Open',
      },
      {
        question: 'What sport is Real Madrid known for besides football?',
        options: ['Basketball', 'Tennis', 'Rugby'],
        answer: 'Basketball',
      },
      {
        question: 'Who is a famous Madrid-born tennis player?',
        options: ['Rafael Nadal', 'Carlos Alcaraz', 'Juan Carlos Ferrero'],
        answer: 'Carlos Alcaraz',
      },
      {
        question: "What is the name of Madrid's famous annual marathon?",
        options: ['Madrid Marathon', 'Barcelona Marathon', 'Valencia Marathon'],
        answer: 'Madrid Marathon',
      },
      {
        question: 'Which cycling event passes through Madrid every year?',
        options: ['Tour de France', 'Vuelta a España', "Giro d'Italia"],
        answer: 'Vuelta a España',
      },
      {
        question:
          'What is the name of the Madrid-based basketball team that competes in the EuroLeague?',
        options: ['Barcelona', 'Real Madrid', 'Valencia Basket'],
        answer: 'Real Madrid',
      },
      {
        question: 'Which famous racecourse is located in Madrid?',
        options: [
          'Hipódromo de La Zarzuela',
          'Hipódromo de San Sebastián',
          'Hipódromo de Sevilla',
        ],
        answer: 'Hipódromo de La Zarzuela',
      },
    ],
    success:
      "The Spanish Golden Age and Madrid's Rise as the Capital\n\nThe 16th and 17th centuries, known as the Spanish Golden Age, marked a period of immense cultural, political, and economic growth for Spain, and it was during this time that Madrid transformed into the capital of the Spanish Empire. In 1561, King Philip II moved the royal court from Toledo to Madrid, solidifying the city's status as the political and administrative heart of Spain.\n\nThis decision to make Madrid the capital was largely influenced by its central location, which allowed for better control of the vast Spanish territories. The city quickly grew, as noble families, merchants, and artisans flocked to be near the royal court. Madrid became a hub of artistic and intellectual activity, attracting writers, painters, and scholars. Iconic figures like Miguel de Cervantes and Diego Velázquez flourished during this era, leaving a lasting legacy on Spanish culture.\n\nThe city underwent significant urban development, with the construction of royal palaces, grand squares like Plaza Mayor, and important religious buildings. Madrid's new role as the capital not only elevated its political importance but also made it a cultural center, where the wealth and power of the Spanish Empire were on full display. By the end of the Golden Age, Madrid had firmly established itself as the beating heart of Spain.",
  },
  {
    score: 0,
    id: 5,
    name: 'Gastronomy of Madrid',
    isActive: false,
    coordinates: { latitude: 40.4154, longitude: -3.7089 }, // Coordinates for Mercado de San Miguel
    questions: [
      {
        question:
          'What is the traditional dish made with chickpeas and vegetables from Madrid?',
        options: ['Gazpacho', 'Cocido Madrileño', 'Tortilla Española'],
        answer: 'Cocido Madrileño',
      },
      {
        question:
          'What is the popular Spanish appetizer consisting of small dishes?',
        options: ['Raciones', 'Tapas', 'Pintxos'],
        answer: 'Tapas',
      },
      {
        question:
          'What dessert is a specialty of Madrid, made with a pastry cream filling?',
        options: ['Churros', 'Porras', 'Crema Catalana'],
        answer: 'Crema Catalana',
      },
      {
        question: 'What drink is typically served with tapas in Madrid?',
        options: ['Sangria', 'Mojito', 'Caipirinha'],
        answer: 'Sangria',
      },
      {
        question:
          'What is the name of the famous Madrid market known for food?',
        options: [
          'Mercado de San Miguel',
          'Mercado de Vallehermoso',
          'Mercado de Antón Martín',
        ],
        answer: 'Mercado de San Miguel',
      },
      {
        question:
          'What is the name of the traditional Spanish omelet made with potatoes?',
        options: ['Tortilla Española', 'Frittata', 'Quiche'],
        answer: 'Tortilla Española',
      },
      {
        question:
          'What is the name of the Spanish rice dish cooked with seafood?',
        options: ['Risotto', 'Paella', 'Arroz con Pollo'],
        answer: 'Paella',
      },
      {
        question:
          'What is the main ingredient in the dish "callos a la madrileña"?',
        options: ['Chickpeas', 'Tripe', 'Lentils'],
        answer: 'Tripe',
      },
      {
        question: 'What type of meat is commonly used in Spanish stews?',
        options: ['Pork', 'Chicken', 'Beef'],
        answer: 'Pork',
      },
      {
        question:
          'What is the name of the popular Spanish drink made from wine and fruit?',
        options: ['Tinto de Verano', 'Sangria', 'Agua de Valencia'],
        answer: 'Sangria',
      },
    ],
    success:
      "Madrid in the Habsburg Era\n\nThe Habsburg dynasty, which ruled Spain from the early 16th to the late 17th century, left a profound mark on Madrid's history. When King Charles I, the first Habsburg monarch of Spain, inherited the Spanish crown in 1516, the foundations were laid for Madrid's future prominence. However, it was under Philip II, his son, that Madrid was officially declared the capital of the Spanish Empire in 1561.\n\nDuring the Habsburg era, Madrid evolved from a modest town into a bustling metropolis. The city's landscape transformed significantly as the monarchy invested in grand architectural projects to reflect the empire's power. Notable constructions included the Royal Alcázar of Madrid and the Plaza Mayor, which became central to Madrid's social and political life. The Habsburg rulers, particularly Philip III and Philip IV, continued to embellish the city, commissioning palaces, churches, and monasteries.\n\nCulturally, this period saw the flourishing of Spain's Golden Age, with Madrid becoming a center for art, literature, and theater. Iconic figures like playwright Lope de Vega and painter Diego Velázquez were closely associated with the court. The Baroque style dominated architecture and art, and Madrid's role as the heart of the empire allowed it to attract talents from across Spain and beyond.\n\nHowever, by the late 17th century, the decline of the Spanish Habsburgs, marked by weak leadership and economic difficulties, left the city struggling. Despite this, the legacy of the Habsburg era in Madrid is visible to this day, with its historic buildings and rich cultural heritage defining much of the city's identity.",
  },
  {
    score: 0,
    id: 6,
    name: 'Festivals and Events in Madrid',
    isActive: false,
    coordinates: { latitude: 40.4169, longitude: -3.7040 }, // Coordinates for Puerta del Sol, where many events take place
    questions: [
      {
        question: "What is the name of Madrid's largest music festival?",
        options: ['Mad Cool Festival', 'Primavera Sound', 'Coachella'],
        answer: 'Mad Cool Festival',
      },
      {
        question: 'Which festival celebrates the patron saint of Madrid?',
        options: ['La Tomatina', 'San Isidro', 'Las Fallas'],
        answer: 'San Isidro',
      },
      {
        question:
          "What is the name of the event that takes place on New Year's Eve in Puerta del Sol?",
        options: ['Midnight Mass', 'Nochevieja', 'Carnaval'],
        answer: 'Nochevieja',
      },
      {
        question: 'Which festival features fireworks and parades in Madrid?',
        options: ['Carnaval', 'Fiesta de San Isidro', 'Día de Muertos'],
        answer: 'Fiesta de San Isidro',
      },
      {
        question: 'What event takes place in Madrid every September?',
        options: ['Festival of Lights', 'Madrid Fashion Week', 'Semana Santa'],
        answer: 'Madrid Fashion Week',
      },
      {
        question:
          'What is the name of the annual food festival held in Madrid?',
        options: ['Madrid Food Festival', 'Gastronomy Week', 'Food Revolution'],
        answer: 'Madrid Food Festival',
      },
      {
        question: 'Which holiday is celebrated on December 6 in Madrid?',
        options: ['Christmas', 'Día de la Constitución', "New Year's Eve"],
        answer: 'Día de la Constitución',
      },
      {
        question: 'What cultural event showcases local artisans and crafts?',
        options: [
          'Mercado de Motores',
          'Feria de Artesanía',
          'Mercado de San Miguel',
        ],
        answer: 'Feria de Artesanía',
      },
    ],
    success:
      "Madrid in the 18th Century: The Bourbon Rule\n\nThe 18th century marked an era of significant changes and modernization for Madrid under the Bourbon dynasty, which came to power after the War of the Spanish Succession. The first monarch of this new dynasty was Philip V, whose arrival heralded a new chapter in the city's history.\n\nThe Bourbons brought with them the ideas of the Enlightenment, which were reflected in large-scale projects aimed at transforming the capital. The reign of Charles III, one of the most notable kings of the dynasty, was particularly important for the development of Madrid. He is often referred to as \"the best mayor of Madrid\" due to his active involvement in the city's improvement. Under his leadership, iconic structures such as the Puerta de Alcalá, the Royal Botanical Garden, the Prado Museum, and the aqueduct were built, enhancing the quality of life for the city's inhabitants.\n\nThe Bourbons aimed to turn Madrid into a modern European city. Roads were improved, street lighting was introduced, and new parks and squares were created. Special attention was paid to the city's aesthetics: architecture became more symmetrical and grand, inspired by French and Italian styles.\n\nThe economy and culture also flourished during the Bourbon era. Court life in Madrid thrived, and Spain began to integrate into the broader European political and cultural landscape. The reforms of Charles III helped strengthen Madrid's position as the capital and transformed it into one of the cultural and political centers of Europe.\n\nThus, the 18th century and the Bourbon rule represented a time of prosperity, modernization, and cultural uplift for Madrid, solidifying the city's status as the capital of the Spanish Empire.",
  },
  {
    score: 0,
    id: 7,
    name: 'Famous People from Madrid',
    isActive: false,
    coordinates: { latitude: 40.4141, longitude: -3.6921 }, // Coordinates for Prado Museum, associated with many famous artists
    questions: [
      {
        question: 'Who was a famous Spanish painter born in Madrid?',
        options: ['Pablo Picasso', 'Francisco Goya', 'Salvador Dalí'],
        answer: 'Francisco Goya',
      },
      {
        question:
          'Which famous author wrote "Don Quixote" and was born near Madrid?',
        options: [
          'Miguel de Cervantes',
          'Gabriel García Márquez',
          'Federico García Lorca',
        ],
        answer: 'Miguel de Cervantes',
      },
      {
        question:
          'Who is a famous Spanish singer known for her flamenco music?',
        options: ['Rosalía', 'Shakira', 'Ana Belén'],
        answer: 'Rosalía',
      },
      {
        question:
          'Which famous Spanish actor starred in "The Others" and "Vicky Cristina Barcelona"?',
        options: ['Javier Bardem', 'Antonio Banderas', 'Eduardo Noriega'],
        answer: 'Eduardo Noriega',
      },
      {
        question:
          'Who is a renowned Spanish architect known for his works in Madrid?',
        options: ['Antoni Gaudí', 'Santiago Calatrava', 'Rafael Moneo'],
        answer: 'Santiago Calatrava',
      },
      {
        question: 'What famous tennis player was born in Madrid?',
        options: ['Rafael Nadal', 'Carlos Alcaraz', 'David Ferrer'],
        answer: 'Carlos Alcaraz',
      },
      {
        question:
          'Who was the Spanish filmmaker known for movies like "Talk to Her"?',
        options: ['Pedro Almodóvar', 'Alejandro Amenábar', 'Luis Buñuel'],
        answer: 'Pedro Almodóvar',
      },
      {
        question: 'Which famous Spanish actress starred in "Vanilla Sky"?',
        options: ['Penélope Cruz', 'Salma Hayek', 'Paz Vega'],
        answer: 'Penélope Cruz',
      },
      {
        question:
          'Who was a prominent Spanish playwright and poet from Madrid?',
        options: [
          'Federico García Lorca',
          'Antonio Buero Vallejo',
          'Miguel de Unamuno',
        ],
        answer: 'Federico García Lorca',
      },
      {
        question:
          'What famous Spanish footballer is known for playing for Real Madrid?',
        options: ['Xavi Hernández', 'Raúl González', 'Andrés Iniesta'],
        answer: 'Raúl González',
      },
    ],
    success:
      "Madrid During the Napoleonic Wars\n\nThe Napoleonic Wars (1803-1815) had a significant impact on Spain and, in particular, on Madrid, which became the center of the struggle for independence. The conflict began when Napoleon Bonaparte intervened in Spanish affairs, taking advantage of internal contradictions and instability in the country.\n\nIn 1808, Napoleon invaded Spain and forced King Charles IV to abdicate. The Spanish, unhappy with French influence and the loss of their monarch, began organizing resistance. As a result, on May 2, 1808, an uprising against French troops took place in Madrid, known as the May 2 Uprising. This event became a symbol of the Spanish people's struggle for their independence.\n\nFrench troops brutally suppressed the uprising, leading to bloodshed and suffering among the local population. However, the uprising catalyzed the formation of guerrilla groups and a movement for independence that spread throughout the country. The May 2 Uprising inspired other regions of Spain to fight against the French.\n\nFor the next few years, Madrid remained under the control of French troops, but the Spanish continued to resist. The city became a battleground, and life for its residents changed dramatically: many inhabitants became refugees, and the economy suffered severely.\n\nIn 1814, after several years of brutal fighting and international pressure, Napoleon was forced to retreat, and Spanish forces regained control of Madrid. Restoring control over the city marked an important stage in the country's recovery process after the war.",
  },
  {
    score: 0,
    id: 8,
    name: 'Architecture of Madrid',
    isActive: false,
    coordinates: { latitude: 40.4200, longitude: -3.6883 }, // Coordinates for Gran Via, known for its architecture
    questions: [
      {
        question:
          'What is the architectural style of the Royal Palace in Madrid?',
        options: ['Baroque', 'Gothic', 'Neoclassical'],
        answer: 'Baroque',
      },
      {
        question:
          'Which building is a prominent example of modern architecture in Madrid?',
        options: ['Torre Picasso', 'Torre de Madrid', 'Edificio España'],
        answer: 'Torre de Madrid',
      },
      {
        question:
          'What is the name of the famous square surrounded by historic buildings?',
        options: ['Plaza Mayor', 'Plaza de Cibeles', 'Plaza de la Villa'],
        answer: 'Plaza Mayor',
      },
      {
        question: 'Which famous architect designed the CaixaForum in Madrid?',
        options: ['Norman Foster', 'Herzog & de Meuron', 'Frank Gehry'],
        answer: 'Herzog & de Meuron',
      },
      {
        question:
          'What is the name of the famous bridge in Madrid that connects two parks?',
        options: ['Puente de Segovia', 'Puente del Rey', 'Puente de Toledo'],
        answer: 'Puente de Toledo',
      },
      {
        question:
          'Which architectural feature is commonly found in traditional Madrid homes?',
        options: ['Balconies', 'Spires', 'Turrets'],
        answer: 'Balconies',
      },
      {
        question: 'What is the main architectural style of the Gran Vía?',
        options: ['Art Deco', 'Gothic', 'Renaissance'],
        answer: 'Art Deco',
      },
      {
        question: 'Which museum in Madrid is housed in a former hospital?',
        options: [
          'Museo del Prado',
          'Museo Thyssen-Bornemisza',
          'Museo Reina Sofía',
        ],
        answer: 'Museo Reina Sofía',
      },
      {
        question: 'What is the name of the landmark clock tower in Madrid?',
        options: [
          'Torre de Madrid',
          'Puerta del Sol Clock',
          'Torre de Cibeles',
        ],
        answer: 'Puerta del Sol Clock',
      },
      {
        question: 'Which modern skyscraper is known as the "Beckham Tower"?',
        options: ['Torre Espacio', 'Torre de Cristal', 'Torre Caja Madrid'],
        answer: 'Torre Espacio',
      },
    ],
    success:
      "Industrialization and Growth of Madrid in the 19th Century\n\nIn the 19th century, Madrid underwent significant changes, becoming a center of industrialization and growth. Following the Napoleonic Wars, the city began to actively rebuild, with authorities investing in infrastructure development: roads, bridges, and railways were constructed. In 1851, the first railway line connecting Madrid to other regions was opened.\n\nThe growth of industry led to the establishment of factories, attracting workers from rural areas. Madrid saw the development of the textile, metallurgy, and food industries, contributing to economic growth. The city's population increased significantly, and by the end of the century, Madrid had become one of the largest cities in Europe.\n\nHowever, rapid growth also brought social issues, such as housing shortages and declining living conditions. Workers began to organize into unions, demanding better working conditions. Thus, the 19th century was a time of profound changes that shaped the future of Madrid.",
  },
  {
    score: 0,
    id: 9,
    name: 'Transportation in Madrid',
    isActive: false,
    coordinates: { latitude: 40.4065, longitude: -3.6895 }, // Coordinates for Atocha Station
    questions: [
      {
        question: "What is the name of Madrid's metro system?",
        options: ['Metro de Madrid', 'Subte de Madrid', 'Tren de Madrid'],
        answer: 'Metro de Madrid',
      },
      {
        question: 'Which airport serves Madrid?',
        options: [
          'Barcelona Airport',
          'Adolfo Suárez Madrid-Barajas Airport',
          'Valencia Airport',
        ],
        answer: 'Adolfo Suárez Madrid-Barajas Airport',
      },
      {
        question: 'What is the name of the main train station in Madrid?',
        options: [
          'Estación de Atocha',
          'Estación de Chamartín',
          'Estación de Sol',
        ],
        answer: 'Estación de Atocha',
      },
      {
        question:
          'Which public transportation option is popular for short distances in Madrid?',
        options: ['Taxi', 'Tram', 'Bicycle'],
        answer: 'Taxi',
      },
      {
        question: 'What is the main bus company serving Madrid?',
        options: ['EMT Madrid', 'ALSA', 'Avanza'],
        answer: 'EMT Madrid',
      },
      {
        question:
          'Which is the fastest way to travel from Madrid to Barcelona?',
        options: ['Bus', 'Train', 'Car'],
        answer: 'Train',
      },
      {
        question: 'What is the name of the bike-sharing program in Madrid?',
        options: ['BiciMAD', 'CycloMAD', 'Madrid Bici'],
        answer: 'BiciMAD',
      },
      {
        question:
          'What is the main avenue that connects several neighborhoods in Madrid?',
        options: ['Gran Vía', 'Paseo de la Castellana', 'Calle de Alcalá'],
        answer: 'Gran Vía',
      },
      {
        question: 'How can you pay for public transport in Madrid?',
        options: [
          'Only with cash',
          'Only with a credit card',
          'With a travel card',
        ],
        answer: 'With a travel card',
      },
      {
        question:
          'What is the typical duration of a metro ride within the city?',
        options: ['10-20 minutes', '30-40 minutes', '1 hour'],
        answer: '10-20 minutes',
      },
    ],
    success:
      "Madrid During the Spanish Civil War (1936-1939)\n\nThe Spanish Civil War (1936-1939) left a deep mark on Madrid's history, turning it into one of the main fronts of the conflict. From the very beginning of the war, the capital became a symbol of resistance against fascism and right-wing dictatorship. In July 1936, following the uprising led by General Francisco Franco, mass protests erupted in Madrid, and the local population took up arms to defend the Republic.\n\nBy 1937, Madrid was subjected to intense bombing by Franco's forces and their allies, including Nazi Germany and fascist Italy. Civilian targets and residential areas were attacked, resulting in a high number of casualties among the civilian population. During this time, the city became an important cultural and political center for Republicans, hosting various organizations, groups, and artists, including notable figures like Ernesto \"Che\" Guevara and the painter Pablo Picasso.\n\nDespite the difficult conditions, Madrid continued to resist until 1939. However, in March 1939, the city fell under the onslaught of Franco's forces, marking the end of the Civil War and the beginning of a long period of dictatorship. The Civil War left deep wounds in Madrid, but it also became a source of inspiration for future generations fighting for freedom and democracy.",
  },
  {
    score: 0,
    id: 10,
    name: 'Nature and Parks in Madrid',
    isActive: false,
    coordinates: { latitude: 40.4153, longitude: -3.6845 }, // Coordinates for Retiro Park
    questions: [
      {
        question:
          'What is the name of the famous park in the center of Madrid?',
        options: ['Casa de Campo', 'Retiro Park', 'Parque del Oeste'],
        answer: 'Retiro Park',
      },
      {
        question: 'Which park in Madrid is known for its large lake?',
        options: [
          'Retiro Park',
          'Parque del Oeste',
          'Parque de la Casa de Campo',
        ],
        answer: 'Retiro Park',
      },
      {
        question: 'What type of trees are commonly found in Retiro Park?',
        options: ['Palm trees', 'Oak trees', 'Birch trees'],
        answer: 'Oak trees',
      },
      {
        question: 'Which park is located on the banks of the Manzanares River?',
        options: ['Madrid Rio', 'Casa de Campo', 'Retiro Park'],
        answer: 'Madrid Rio',
      },
      {
        question: 'What is the main feature of the Casa de Campo?',
        options: ['Zoo', 'Museum', 'Amusement park'],
        answer: 'Zoo',
      },
      {
        question: 'Which garden is known for its beautiful rose collection?',
        options: [
          'Royal Botanical Garden',
          'Sabatini Gardens',
          'Parque de El Capricho',
        ],
        answer: 'Royal Botanical Garden',
      },
      {
        question: 'What is the name of the annual event held in Retiro Park?',
        options: ['Festival de Flores', 'Madrid Book Fair', 'Feria de Abril'],
        answer: 'Madrid Book Fair',
      },
      {
        question: 'Which nature reserve is located near Madrid?',
        options: [
          'Parque Nacional de la Sierra de Guadarrama',
          'Parque Natural de las Tablas de Daimiel',
          'Parque Nacional de Cabañeros',
        ],
        answer: 'Parque Nacional de la Sierra de Guadarrama',
      },
      {
        question: 'What is the name of the famous viewpoint in Madrid?',
        options: [
          'Teleférico de Madrid',
          'Mirador del Castillo de Manzanares',
          'Mirador de San Nicolás',
        ],
        answer: 'Mirador del Castillo de Manzanares',
      },
      {
        question: "What is the most common animal spotted in Madrid's parks?",
        options: ['Fox', 'Squirrel', 'Deer'],
        answer: 'Squirrel',
      },
    ],
    success:
      'Modern Madrid: From Dictatorship to Democracy and Transformation into a Megacity\n\nThe transition of Madrid from a dictatorship to a modern democratic city is a remarkable chapter in its history. Following the end of the Spanish Civil War in 1939, Madrid came under the authoritarian rule of Francisco Franco, who imposed a regime characterized by repression and censorship. For decades, the city endured a cultural and political stagnation that stifled innovation and growth.\n\nWith Franco\'s death in 1975, Spain entered a period of democratic transition, known as the "Transition to Democracy." Madrid became the epicenter of this transformation, where political, social, and cultural movements flourished. The legalization of political parties, freedom of the press, and the establishment of democratic institutions marked a significant turning point. In 1978, Spain adopted a new constitution, solidifying its commitment to democracy and individual rights.\n\nAs democracy took root, Madrid experienced rapid urbanization and economic growth. The city expanded its infrastructure, attracting businesses and international investment. The 1980s and 1990s saw Madrid emerge as a cultural hub, hosting numerous art exhibitions, music festivals, and international events. This period also saw the development of modern transport systems, such as the Madrid Metro, which enhanced connectivity and accessibility.\n\nToday, Madrid is a vibrant megacity, known for its rich cultural heritage, diverse population, and dynamic economy. The city boasts a blend of historical landmarks and modern architecture, symbolizing its journey from the shadows of dictatorship to the forefront of democracy in Europe. As it continues to grow and evolve, Madrid remains a testament to resilience and the power of civic engagement in shaping a better future.',
  },
];